There's no time left.
They found me.
I can't leave.
Which will come first, tomorrow or an accident?
They found me.
You don't seem very happy.
It's pathetic to be colleagues with someone like you.
No secrets at all.
Is it because of the anonymous message about
Xu Qiaoyue's MO?
There are no clues so far.
I knew it wouldn't be that easy.
Many things in this world
are not as bad as you think.
Don't be so pessimistic.
The truth
never lies.
I hope it's really like you said.
Thank you.
You actually say thank you?
Do you think
I don't even have this basic manners?
That's not what I meant.
I'm just
not good with words.
Alright, don't say anything.
Drink up.
But I can't drink.
You can't drink?
Why are you holding a bottle then?
Anyway,
since we set up the Accident Investigation Team,
everything has gone smoothly.
I hope we can soon find
the answers to the doubts
in our hearts.
Hello?
Drunk already?
An accident.
Sobered up.
Morning.
These are all from the past year,
all the accident cases I've solved.
They were actually all murders.
I didn't expect you to be the first to find it out.
This is the electrical leakage case.
This is the fatal dentist allergy case.
I noticed.
They all share a common trait.
Someone deliberately planned and guided them.
They named their organization Lighthouse.
They're just a bunch of outlaws claiming to be righteous,
fighting evil with evil,
and putting themselves above the law.
Have you been investigating Lighthouse
because they hurt someone close to you?
Like your sister?
You managed to deduce that?
No.
Bai Xiaolin told me.
I thought you were a genius.
That blabbermouth.
Can you tell me about it?
Maybe I can help you.
It all started a year ago.
Sister.
Zhuang Qing.
Instead of studying hard abroad,
why did you come back so suddenly?
Did something happen?
We have a holiday.
Why won't you even let me come home?
Am I not letting you come home?
The point is, it's not holiday time at your school.
Your sister is a police officer.
Lying to me is useless.
Tell the truth, what's going on?
Or else I'll throw you out.
Sister,
my school is closed for the anniversary.
Sister.
I'm hungry.
I want to eat the noodles you cook.
I'll settle the score with you later.
Just wait.
Eat up, you little glutton.
Eat slowly.
You're like this every time.
Wolfing down your food,
not like a little girl at all.
Eat slowly.
Zhuang Qing.
Zhuang Qing,
why are you crying?
I'm fine, Sister.
The noodles you made
are just too delicious.
Eat up.
Chief Sang, I know.
Okay.
Sister.
Okay, I'll be right there, Chief Sang.
Okay, I understand.
You.
What am I going to do with you?
You even lied to me about the anniversary,
about having a holiday.
The principal has already told me.
You haven't been to school for a long time, have you?
If you still don't go,
you will be expelled.
Do you realize the severity of this?
Let's go.
Sister,
what if I don't go to school anymore
and be a police officer
just like you?
Be a police officer like me?
You?
You haven't even graduated from college.
How can you be a police officer like me?
Sister,
aren't you afraid you won't see me again?
Just to play around,
you actually made up such a thing.
You're really something.
Sister, if I marry a rich kid,
you will never see me again.
That would be great.
I would finally be free.
I don't have that much time to see you off.
Hurry up and find your rich kid.
Sister,
I'll miss you.
You,
you're a big girl now.
You can't be so playful anymore.
Why are you always so willful?
I promise you,
I'll definitely visit you when I have time.
I don't have time to waste with you.
Just leave.
I didn't expect
that my decision at the time
would end up hurting Zhuang Qing.
She didn't leave.
Instead, she went to the café we used to frequent.
This café
used to be Zhuang Qing's and my favorite place.
It holds so many of our shared memories.
In my eyes,
she will always be that
little girl who never grows up,
always waiting here for me to come back.
But ever since her accident,
I've never been back here.
If only I had cared for her more in the past.
Or rather,
if I hadn't driven her away that day,
would she have been fine?
Thinking back,
her appearance,
her actions,
her emotions,
all seemed so abnormal.
I should have noticed it earlier.
But until she died in front of me,
I didn't realize it.
Perhaps,
she had already foreseen her own death.
So,
your current sadness
comes more from
guilt.
Probably both.
So this case
eventually went nowhere.
There was no case at all.
After the accident,
the driver already said
that it was his negligence that day
that led to Zhuang Qing's death.
But I really don't believe it.
I can't accept this result.
But I investigated for a long time,
and ultimately, all the evidence pointed to
this being an accident.
But you kept investigating,
and even
set up a department.
Because of this.
This was left behind when Zhuang Qing died.
Maybe
she wanted to leave some information for me.
There is no time.
They have found me.
I can't leave.
Between an accident and tomorrow,
which will come first?
Understood.
I understand all your intentions.
You suspect
that this accident
was designed by the lighthouse,
right?
Although there is no direct proof in this case,
But judging from Zhuang Qing's
abnormal behavior at that time,
this was definitely no accident.
It must be related to the Lighthouse.
If they remain at large,
there will be more victims like Xu Qiaoyue
who become tools for them to escape the law
and carry out criminal plans.
As a police officer,
I will never allow such an organization to exist.
So I must keep investigating.
I will set up the Accident Investigation Team.
Mr. Li.
Your room expires tomorrow.
The manager asked me to check
if you'd like to renew.
Mr. Li?
What's that smell?
Mr. Li, I'm coming in.
Mr. Li?
Someone's dead!